Kuroneko...
That's what I called the girl I was friends with when I was a kid.
Hey, did you really see an alien?
Yep.
Then, one day ten years ago, I made two irreversible mistakes.
The first mistake was...
not turning back at that point.
Ryota!
And the second mistake...
Back then...
why did I grab Kuroneko's hand?
Every night since then,
I've watched the sky on my own.
Kuroneko...
I wish I could see you again.
While I Wait For You
Upon entering my junior year of highschool, I set my sights on becoming a researcher at NASA.
Equatorial Telescope
I decided to get as close to space as I could,
and prove that aliens existed in Kuroneko's place.
Equatorial Telescope
That's my way of making it all up to her.
Planisphere
Master the Stars
Say, why are you so sure aliens exist?
Planisphere
Master the Stars
You don't believe in them, so I'm not telling.
I do! If you say they exist...
Well it's 'cause I've met one—
an alien.
What?
I even know where one is right now!
Then take me there!
Fine.
Huh?
If you promise not to tell anyone where it is...
Kuroneko and I always played together.
I loved Kuroneko, and I thought I knew everything about her.
But this was the first time she'd mentioned aliens.
I couldn't believe her.
The alien is up ahead.
Once you see it, you'd better believe me.
Then that accident happened.
Ryota!
When I came to, I was in a hospital.
Miraculously, I was saved.
They told me Kuroneko was safe in another hospital.
What on earth could I say to get her to forgive me?
If we could prove together that aliens existed, maybe she would feel better.
That was all I thought about while I was in the hospital.
Then on the day I got out, they told me the truth.
Kuroneko had fallen off the dam and died instantly.
It's bizarre, but I actually don't know her name.
All I remember are the moles under her arm
and that I called her "Kuroneko."
Good morning!
Morning!
Hello!
Hey, Murakami, did you see?
See what?
In the national mock exam we took, you were the top junior.
But out of all the high schoolers, I was third. Still got a ways to go.
C'mon, don't think that way!
It's amazing. You're the top of the class, Murakami-kun!
Thanks, Kashiwagi-san.
Blunt as usual.
You're always so cold to the girls, Murakami.
Man.
I'm not cold. I just can't handle them.
Hey, homeroom is starting. Hurry up and take your seats.
We have a transfer student to introduce today.
A transfer student? That's rare.
The test to transfer in is incredibly hard.
This is Kuroha Neko-san.
Kuroha... Neko!?
Everyone help her—
Huh? What's wrong, Murakami?
She looks exactly like her.
The vibes she gives off are a little different, but...
She's... gotta be Kuroneko!
That's right! It's not like I ever saw a body.
They just told me she died.
Could it be...
You're alive!?
Huh?
I'm pretty sure this is the first time we've ever met.
No! We were little kids, so you might not remember,
but you and I used to hang out!
Used to?
I can prove it!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Whatever! Just shut up and show me your armpits!
Her armpits?
Whoa, jeez.
Is he serious?
Did Murakami-kun study so hard he went nuts?
I didn't think he was that kind of guy.
Hey, Kuroha.
That uniform is so cute. Is it from your old school?
It's original.
Original?
I guess I just mistook her.
In today's pool lesson, we'll practice swimming underwater.
This isn't a game, so please be careful.
Okay!
Hey, check it out!
Yeah! That is one bangin' body!
I didn't know such a gorgeous high schooler existed!
The other girls at this school only care about studying.
Kuroha, you're fine!
You can stand here!
Hey, look!
Yeah, that angle is a-mazing.
Makes me wanna dive to the girls' side and "accidentally" touch those boobs!
As if that's not a crime...
Next group, are you ready?
Yeah!
Okay, go under!
Kashiwagi-san!
What's wrong?
Teacher! Kashiwagi's leg got sucked into the filter, and she can't get it out!
She can't breathe!
Go tell them to stop the pump!
Ah, okay!
Kashiwagi-san!
Hang in there!
I knew this would happen.
Today, two students at this school...
Oh God, we're not going to make it in time!
are going to die.
She's out! Kashiwagi-san, are you okay?
S-Sensei...
Thank God!
Are you okay?
You'll pull it together!
Man, I thought she was done for.
That was some good luck.
Since the poolside collapsed, the pump got plugged.
Yeah, that kind of thing doesn't happen every day.
And that timing! There's nothing else to call it but luck.
On days like this, the best way to unwind is to look at the stars.
I just can't get it out of my head. I know Kuroha can't be Kuroneko.
She's already dead.
But no matter how many times I remind myself of that fact, it's still hard to accept.
Even though it's been ten years,
I don't want to admit she's gone.
I wish I could just forget all about Kuroneko.
Huh? What are you doing here?
You can look at the stars here?
Y-Yeah.
I guess there was an astronomy boom when Apollo went to the moon.
This is an old observatory built during that wave of popularity.
But now I'm the only member of the astronomy club.
Up until last year there were upperclassmen,
but if no one joins next year, I guess we'll be shut down.
Sorry. You look exactly like a childhood friend of mine.
That's why I said that weird stuff during homeroom.
A childhood friend?
Yeah, a kinda quirky girl who believed in aliens.
But she died, and it was all my fault.
So to search for aliens in her place,
I come here every day to look through the telescope.
I'd like to make one thing clear.
I'm not your childhood friend, and I don't know you at all.
We only just met.
I know that.
So... what did you come here for?
There's something I have to tell you.
Huh?
Today, two students at this school were supposed to die.
What!?
The first was supposed to die in the pool, but she was saved.
Hey, what are you talking about!?
And the other one who is supposed to die...
is you.
What do you mean I'm gonna die?
The last bus leaves at 8:20 PM.
Yeah. That's the bus I always get on.
Don't miss that bus.
If you don't get on that bus, you'll die.
So you're saying I should believe this "prophecy" of yours?
I don't care. Just don't miss it.
Well, I don't need you to tell me to catch the last bus.
If I don't catch it, I can't get home.
Oh? Well, that's good. Guess I'll be going...
How many constellations are there in all?
Oh, those are old constellations. There's a list, isn't there?
This? One, two, three...
You don't have to count.
It's six rows and eight columns, so 48.
Wow, you added them up so fast.
Are you kidding? If you know your multiplication tables, it's a cinch.
What's a multiplication table?
What!?
Huh?
You can't not know! You learn 'em in second grade!
Of course I know multiplication tables! Duh.
I... uh... just don't sit at them very often.
Two times two.
Huh?
If you know your multiplication tables, you should be able to answer!
What's two times two?
What!? Umm...
Twice?
Eight by two?
A two-by-four?
Eight times eight!
Shut the gate?
How did someone who doesn't even know their multiplication tables get into this school!?
Shut up, shut up, shut up! I have my ways! Plenty of them!
"Ways"?
Well, whatever. I'll give you this one. Even if you're a little smarter than me,
I'm definitely way stronger!
Huh?
Did you play sports or something?
Hm? Not really.
What's up with this girl? She's just saying whatever.
There's no way I'll lose to a girl who hasn't even trained.
Come on, I'll arm wrestle you.
Sure.
Okay, let's go.
One, two, three, g—
Ow!
I'm sorry! I didn't control my strength very well.
Lemme see your arm!
She's not particularly muscular.
More like scrawny!
What are you blushing for?
N-No one's ever touched me like that before!
Wouldn't you get nervous?
Huh?
Don't get weird on me.
Actually, now that I get a good look at her, she's actually pretty cute.
Well, that makes sense. She looks just like Kuroneko. Totally my type.
Are you satisfied now?
No, I'm not. Lemme see you flex.
Huh? Flex?
Yeah. Give it a shot.
Is that all you got?
How could I lose to a squishy girl like you!?
I dunno! Maybe you're just a wimp!
CQ, CQ. Yeah, it's me. Over.
An amateur radio?
The forecast changed, but now it's even worse. Over.
If it won't make a difference whether
he gets on the bus or not,
then should we just have him die? Over.
Yeah, okay. I'll let him know. Over and out.
Actually, it's fine if you miss the bus.
Hey, what the heck was that about just now?
In fact, forget the bus altogether. Just don't leave the building.
What!?
Since you can't get home if you miss the last bus, spend the night here.
Got it? I warned you, so you'd better believe me.
Once you see it, you'd better believe me.
Let's suppose all the stuff she said is true.
If me getting on the bus or not is the difference between living and dying...
I get it.
If her prediction is correct, it should start raining around here soon.
So much for that! The forecast for today is clear—
It's really raining!?
So I was able to save both of them.
Hang in there, Akane-san! Akane-san!
I'm... not... gonna make it.
Neko, take this and run.
You can forget everything else, but not this.
You're the only one... who can save this world... from ruin.
Akane-san! Akane-san!
Honestly, I don't even know what saving the world from ruin means.
Akane-san! Stay with me! Akane-san! Akane-san!
But saving people I know are going to die is something I can do.
CQ, CQ.
What? No way!
I stayed off the bus like she said, but I left the observatory.
So now, according to her, I'm gonna die.
Do I believe her?
No... but I want to.
Even if it means risking my life, I want to verify that what she said is true firsthand.
If the time it takes to miss the bus makes the difference between life and death...
Well, it's hard to imagine getting mixed up in a crime in such a deserted spot.
If it were a large scale disaster, like an earthquake, there would be other casualties.
So what's a smaller scale disaster that occurs in the rain?
A mudslide!
No way!
Shit! I can't move!
She... She actually knew the future!
This is why I told you not to go home!
You idiot!
What's with this girl?
She split the boulder!?
Jeez, I knew you'd die if you missed the bus.
That's why I warned you.
But the moment you made the decision to catch it, the forecast changed.
If I had gotten on the bus,
the time it was stopped would've meant
the bus and me would've been crushed under the boulder, right?
I could gather that much from what you said.
If the bus had gotten crushed,
way more people would have died.
So you told me not to leave the observatory.
If you figured that much out, why did you come here?
More importantly, who or what are you?
I... I'm...
a magician.
Huh? Don't be ridiculous.
Oh, you don't believe me? Even though you believe in aliens?
Aliens don't go against science.
But magic is the very definition of "unscientific."
Ah... but unless you're a magician,
there's no way to explain all this.
I mean, you split a boulder in half and beat me at arm wrestling with that squishy arm...
Don't pick on me!
Hey, if you're really a magician,
how did you get your powers?
Surgery. That and drugs.
What? That's not magic!
I really wanted... to get by without using my powers.
I ran away from the researchers, so I didn't want anyone to find out I am a magician.
But I couldn't hear a word she was saying.
Somewhere in my heart, I guess I had still been hoping...
"Couldn't Kuroha be Kuroneko, after all?"
But she didn't have Kuroneko's moles.
kagayaku hoshi miagete
Looking up at the sky
Looking up at the sky
kagayaku hoshi miagete
Looking up at the sky
itsumo akogarete tana
I always admired the shining stars.
I always admired the shining stars.
itsumo akogarete tana
I always admired the shining stars.
ashita wo yume minagara
In my dreams of tomorrow
In my dreams of tomorrow
ashita wo yume minagara
In my dreams of tomorrow
koi wo shite mitari
I'll try out love
I'll try out love
koi wo shite mitari
I'll try out love
naimono nedari de
and ask for the moon.
and ask for the moon.
naimono nedari de
and ask for the moon.
shiawase wa hito sorezore to
"Happiness is different for everyone."
"Happiness is different for everyone."
shiawase wa hito sorezore to
"Happiness is different for everyone."
oshietekureta ne
That's what you taught me, right?
That's what you taught me, right?
oshietekureta ne
That's what you taught me, right?
sonna kimi ga suki de
That's what I love about you.
That's what I love about you.
sonna kimi ga suki de
That's what I love about you.
ne
You know?
watashi wa ima koi ni ochita
I have fallen in love
I have fallen in love
watashi wa ima koi ni ochita
I have fallen in love
ichibanboshi
so I ask upon the star
so I ask upon the star
ichibanboshi
so I ask upon the star
onegaishite douka kimi to
to please, please let me
to please, please let me
onegaishite douka kimi to
to please, please let me
itsumo issho ni ireru you ni
stay by your side forever and ever.
i
tsu
mo
i
ssho
stay by your side forever and ever.
tsu
mo
i
ssho
itsumo issho ni ireru you ni
stay by your side forever and ever.
watashi wa ima hajimete shiru
I only now know
I only now know
watashi wa ima hajimete shiru
I only now know
koi wa setsunai
how love can be
how love can be
koi wa setsunai
how love can be
kurushikunaru demo ai wa tottemo hora
so very painful, and yet
so very painful, and yet
kurushikunaru demo ai wa tottemo hora
so very painful, and yet
atatakai mono nanda
so wonderful and warm.
so wonderful and warm.
atatakai mono nanda
so wonderful and warm.